<?xml version="1.0.2" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <name>Max Special Modifiers</name>
  <description>Maximize special modifier affixes on Keropok, Orang Bunian, and Awakened items with configurable forced affixes.

[b]Not recommended for new players.[/b] This is written for seasoned players who want to experiment with their gear and avoid spending tens of hours rerolling.

[h2]What This Mod Does[/h2]

This mod automatically maximizes the special (implicit) affixes for Keropok, Orang Bunian, and Awakened items. You can configure which specific affixes are forced onto these items, giving you total control.

[h2]Key Features[/h2]

[list]
[*][b]Automatic Maximization[/b]: All "special" modifier affixes are set to their maximum possible values
[*][b]Configurable Affixes[/b]: Choose which specific affixes are forced onto your items
[*][b]Three Item Types Supported[/b]: Keropok items, Orang Bunian items, Awakened items
[*][b]Keropok Progression Control[/b]: maximum of 6 random modifiers is ensured
[/list]

[h2]Configuration[/h2]

The mod creates a configuration file after being enabled at:
[code]%USERPROFILE%\AppData\LocalLow\ATATGames\Ghostlore\max-special-modifiers.config.json[/code]
All changes require a restart of the game to take effect. Not just a save reload.

[h3]Simple Configuration Example[/h3]

[code]{
  "DebugLogging": false,
  "Keropok": {
    "Increased buff effect": true,
    "HP Regen": false,
    "Movement Speed": true,
    ...
  },
  "OrangBunian": {
    "Additional Minions": false,
    "Minion Max HP": false,
    "Attack Damage": true,
    ...
  },
  "Awakened": {
    "Minion Damage": false,
    "Cooldown Reduction": true,
    "Critical Hit Multiplier": true,
    ...
  }
}[/code]

[h3]How to Configure[/h3]

[olist]
[*]Start the game with the mod enabled
[*]The configuration file will be created automatically
[*]Close the game and edit the JSON file
[*]Set affixes to true to force them, false to disable them (don't delete)
[*]Restart the game to apply changes
[/olist]

[h2]Troubleshooting[/h2]

[list]
[*][b]Affixes not appearing[/b]: Check that the affix name matches exactly (case-sensitive). They are correct and all present in the initial file
[*][b]Configuration not loading[/b]: Ensure the JSON file is valid and in the correct, original location
[*][b]Debug information[/b]: Set [code]"DebugLogging": true[/code] to see detailed logs in the game console
[*][b]If all else fails[/b]: Delete the config file, restart the game, and try again
[/list]

[h2]Important Notes[/h2]

[list]
[*]Backup your saves before using this mod
[*][b]Seriously, backup your saves before using this mod.[/b] It is new and does complex things that could break your items due to an oversight. It's been tested, but I'm not a professional QA tester, and I'll be amazed if I don't get a bug report.
[*]All affixes are enabled by default 
[*]The mod works with existing saves and is safe to disable.
[/list]

Source code: [url=https://github.com/ggoDeye/ghostlore-max-special-modifiers]https://github.com/ggoDeye/ghostlore-max-special-modifiers[/url]</description>
  <activated>false</activated>
  <publishId>3586437133</publishId>
</ModInfo>
